KENA BEYENE

EMERGING IT PROFESSIONAL

CONTACT INFORMATION

515-423-1628 kenabeyene85@gmail.com

CAREER SUMMARY

Enthusiastic and detailoriented, emerging IT professional with 5+ years of customer service experience. Aiming to use my exceptional communication skills and love for collaborative team environments to excel further as a coder and a leader.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Install and configure hardware and software components to ensure usability.

Troubleshoot software, firmware, networking, and other system problems.

Proficient knowledge in HTML, CSS, & JavaScript.

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Multi-linguistic
Quick Learner
Excellent Writer
Team Leader
Creative Strategist

EDUCATION

NPOWER MISSOURI IT TRAINING PROGRAM - ST. LOUIS

February 2020 – July 2020 Cisco Mobility Fundamentals Certification Pending COMPTIA ITF/A+ Certification

ST. LOUIS COMMUNITY COLLEGE - MERAMEC

January 2018 – May 2019 Dean's List Software Development (C#, SQL, & HTML)

UNIVERSITY OF MISSOURI - ST. LOUIS

August 2016 – May 2017 Pierre Laclede Honors College

WORK EXPERIENCE

THE BELLWETHER, St. Louis, MO – **Assistant, Food runner** February 2020 – Current

Assist servers in providing a high-quality dining experience Handle backhouse cleanliness duties in a timely manner

KEYSTONE EVENT STAFFING, St. Louis, MO - Server

August 2019 – Current

Manage and cater to anywhere from 60-200 people Handle venues at weddings, country clubs, and various banquets

WESTVIEW ASSISTED LIVING & MEMORY CARE, Ellisville, MO – Lead Server

June 2017 – September 2019

Trained new employees, two of which are still employed Managed and prepared dining items alongside directors and cooks